<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 11:28:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Sobriety</title>
      <link>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/a-sober-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/a-sober-life/</guid>
      <description>The first time I tried to write this it was over 6000 words. At the heart of sobriety is the tension between conflict and resolving conflict. Positive action, and negative action. The correct path is not always clear, to me or any anyone else. The writing came to reflect that. One paragraph was a desperate rallying cry against drinking. The next a fitful discussion of mindfulness. What was I trying to say?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This vs That</title>
      <link>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/this-vs-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 10:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/this-vs-that/</guid>
      <description>Some things are traumatic to get started with. It seems that certain tasks are hard to begin, but easy once started. These high resistance tasks tend to be things that we care a lot about. Drawing, exercise, writing, studying to name but a few. You&amp;rsquo;ll recognise some of those tasks in your own mental list of things you don&amp;rsquo;t quite get round too doing. Creative or important work is taxing, and it&amp;rsquo;s all too easy to nudge it down the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Action List</title>
      <link>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/master-action-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/master-action-list/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been keeping a &amp;lsquo;Master Action List&amp;rsquo; to ensure that the key ideas that I discover get implemented. It&amp;rsquo;s a way of resurfacing the applicable concepts from books, courses, videos in one place. Don&amp;rsquo;t store good ideas but actually complete them.
We don&amp;rsquo;t remember a huge amount of what we read. We act on even less of it. I am a veracious reader, reading between 4-6 books a month. Often when a book is particularly powerful, the ideas of the book stick with me forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Book Of Steps</title>
      <link>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/small-steps-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/small-steps-forward/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s hard to see progress A few months a go I was driving my girlfriend crazy. I felt like I was accomplishing nothing. I was working hard than ever and I had nothing to show for it. Or so I thought. I felt like I was putting in the work but I had nothing to show for it. The truth was I couldn&amp;rsquo;t see it. I&amp;rsquo;ve always believed that big results come from committing to long term progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Website Builders cost a lot more than their Price Tag</title>
      <link>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/free-website-builders-will-cost-you-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 14:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/free-website-builders-will-cost-you-more/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m currently accepting projects, get in touch for an estimate &amp;rightarrow;     Customers first point of contact with your business is more and more likely to be your website.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve been looking at getting a new website for your business or project you know they aren&amp;rsquo;t cheap.
Costs range from anywhere from a few hundred to a few thousand pounds. Website builders seem an attractive option for cost conscious business owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your body knows how to move. So move it.</title>
      <link>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/your-body-is-designed-to-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 11:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://h-arry-smith.github.io/articles/your-body-is-designed-to-move/</guid>
      <description>Every new year, this year more than most, we ruminate on the future. For many, this means another yearly attempt at building exercise into their routines.
Often, they fail. I failed every year from 2010 to 2019.
Personal fitness has become a poisoned well of mis-information and cash-grabs. Information is either outdated, complex or designed to mislead you. Gyms leech your finances, paying for equipment you don&amp;rsquo;t understand and don&amp;rsquo;t need.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
